Guide to the Poly Archives Historic Photograph Collection RG.026
Poly Archives at the Bern Dibner Library of Science and Technology, NYU Libraries
- Series VI: Alumni, 11738
  - Subseries B: Alumni Association, 13237
    - Annual Meeting 2000, 2000 June 6; cuid558; 11752 (Box 13, Folder 47)
    - Alumni Chapter Meetings, 2001; cuid559; 11739 (Box 13, Folder 48)
    - Alumni Meeting, Nassau-Suffolk Section, 1964 June 6; cuid560; 13161 (Box 13, Folder 49)
    - Mohawk Valley Section, 1950-1954; cuid561; 13317 (Box 13, Folder 50)
    - Sections, P.S.L.I., 1960s; cuid562; 13318 (Box 13, Folder 51)
  - Subseries C: Alumni Events, 13238
    - Annual Banquets & Dinners, 1967-1982; cuid563; 11921 (Box 13, Folder 52)
    - Alumni Dinner 1949, cuid564; 11740 (Box 13, Folder 53)
    - Alumni Dinner 1991, cuid565; 11788 (Box 13, Folder 54)
    - Long Island Alumni Dinner, 1987 September; cuid566; 13319 (Box 13, Folder 55)
    - Alumni Banquet 1943, cuid567; 12054 (Box 13, Folder 56)
    - Alumni Banquet 1952, cuid568; 12055 (Box 13, Folder 57)
    - Alumni Banquet 1953, cuid569; 12056 (Box 13, Folder 58)
    - Alumni Banquet 1954, cuid570; 12057 (Box 13, Folder 59)
    - Alumni Banquet 1955, cuid571; 12058 (Box 13, Folder 60)
    - Alumni Day & Banquet 1956, cuid572; 11741 (Box 13, Folder 61)
    - Alumni Banquet 1957, cuid573; 12059 (Box 13, Folder 62)
    - Alumni Banquet 1958, cuid574; 12060 (Box 13, Folder 63)
    - Alumni Banquet 1959, cuid575; 12061 (Box 13, Folder 64)
    - Alumni Banquet 1960, cuid576; 12062 (Box 13, Folder 65)
    - Alumni Banquet 1963, cuid577; 12063 (Box 13, Folder 66)
    - Alumni Banquet 1964, 1964 February 15; cuid578; 12064 (Box 13, Folder 67)
    - Alumni Banquet 1965, 1965 March 13; cuid579; 12065 (Box 13, Folder 68)
    - Alumni Banquet 1966, 1966 March 12; cuid580; 12066 (Box 13, Folder 69)
    - Alumni Banquet 1967, 1967 March 11; cuid581; 12067 (Box 13, Folder 70)
    - Alumni Banquet 1968, cuid582; 12068 (Box 13, Folder 71)
    - Alumni Banquet 1969, cuid583; 12069 (Box 13, Folder 72)
    - Alumni Banquet 1970, cuid584; 12070 (Box 13, Folder 73)
    - Alumni Banquet 1971, cuid585; 12071 (Box 13, Folder 74)
    - Alumni Banquet 1972, cuid586; 12072 (Box 13, Folder 75)
    - Alumni Banquet 1973, cuid587; 12073 (Box 13, Folder 76)
    - Alumni Banquet 1974, cuid588; 13585 (Box 13, Folder 77)
    - Alumni Banquet Miscellaneous, undated; cuid589; 12053 (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - Alumni Day 1957-1958, cuid590; 11742 (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - Alumni Day 1959, 1959 May 16; cuid591; 11743 (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - Alumni Day 1960, cuid592; 11744 (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - Alumni Day 1962-1963, cuid593; 11745 (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - Alumni Day 1964, 1964 May 9; cuid594; 11746 (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - Alumni Day 1965, 1965 March 22; cuid595; 11747 (Box 14, Folder 7)
    - Alumni Day 1966, 1966 April 30; cuid596; 11748 (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - Alumni Dance 1964- Long Island, cuid597; 11786 (Box 14, Folder 9)
    - Alumni Event 1994, 1994 February; cuid598; 11782 (Box 14, Folder 10)
    - Alumni Event 1996, cuid599; 11783 (Box 14, Folder 11)
    - Alumni Event 1996- Big Apple Chapter, cuid600; 11784 (Box 14, Folder 12)
    - Alumni Event 2001, 2001 June 5; cuid601; 11785 (Box 14, Folder 13)
    - Alumni NASA Tour, 1999; cuid602; 12807 (Box 14, Folder 14)
    - Alumni-Student Mixer 1998, 1998 November 12; cuid603; 12710 (Box 14, Folder 15)
    - Alumni-Student Mixer 1999, 1999 February 3; cuid604; 12711 (Box 14, Folder 16)
    - Alumni-Student Mixer 1999, 1999 February 3; cuid605; 12712 (Box 14, Folder 17)
    - Alumni-Student Mixer 1999, 1999 November 11; cuid606; 11767 (Box 14, Folder 18)
    - Alumni-Student Mixer 2000, 2000 March 30; cuid607; 11765 (Box 14, Folder 19)
    - Alumni-Student Mixer 2000, 2000 November 9; cuid608; 11766 (Box 14, Folder 20)
    - Distinguished Alumnus Award 1996- Charles Hinkaty, 1996 June 6; cuid609; 11762 (Box 14, Folder 21)
    - Distinguished Alumnus Award 1999- Herbert Henkel, 1999 September 27; cuid610; 11763 (Box 14, Folder 22)
    - Distinguished Alumnus Award 2000- Dr. Tai-Lin Hsu, 2000 October; cuid611; 11764 (Box 14, Folder 23)
    - Distinctive Alumni, undated; cuid612; 13321 (Box 14, Folder 24)
    - Outstanding Alumni Lunch, undated; cuid613; 11792 (Box 14, Folder 25)
    - Outstanding Alumnus- Math Award, 1997 December 11; cuid614; 13322 (Box 14, Folder 26)
    - Student-Alumni Conference 1966, 1966 February 15; cuid615; 11794 (Box 14, Folder 27)
    - Student-Alumni Conference 1966, 1966 October 3; cuid616; 11793 (Box 14, Folder 28)
    - Student-Alumni Conference (ESO), undated; cuid617; 11916 (Box 14, Folder 29)
  - Subseries D: Alumni Leadership Seminar, 13239
    - Alumni Leadership Seminar, 1995 October 2; cuid618; 11768 (Box 14, Folder 30)
    - Alumni Leadership Seminar, John Sie, 1995 October 23; cuid619; 11769 (Box 14, Folder 31)
    - Alumni Leadership Seminar, Rachel Freidman, 1996 October 10; cuid620; 11756 (Box 14, Folder 32)
    - Alumni Leadership Seminar, William Mow, 1996- November 4; cuid621; 11754 (Box 14, Folder 33)
    - Alumni Leadership Seminar, John Giba, 1996 November 11; cuid622; 11757 (Box 14, Folder 34)
    - Alumni Leadership Seminar, Leon Levy, 1998 May 1; cuid623; 11755 (Box 14, Folder 35)
    - Alumni Leadership Seminar, Gerald Ross, 1998 September 25; cuid624; 11770 (Box 14, Folder 36)
    - Alumni Leadership Seminar,Nicholas Reitenbach, 1998 October 26; cuid625; 11771 (Box 14, Folder 37)
    - Alumni Leadership Seminar, Charles Souter, 1998 November 18; cuid626; 11772 (Box 14, Folder 38)
    - Alumni Leadership Seminar, Daniel Greenberg, 1999; cuid627; 11758 (Box 14, Folder 39)
    - Alumni Leadership Lunch, 1999 March; cuid628; 11761 (Box 14, Folder 40)
    - Alumni Leadership Seminar, Robert Prieto, 1999 March 11; cuid629; 11773 (Box 14, Folder 41)
    - Alumni Leadership Seminar, Stanley Beige, 1999 April 4; cuid630; 11774 (Box 14, Folder 42)
    - Alumni Leadership Seminar, Joseph Owades, 1999 April 21; cuid631; 11775 (Box 14, Folder 43)
    - Alumni Leadership Seminar, David Sobin, 1999 September 29; cuid632; 11776 (Box 14, Folder 44)
    - Alumni Leadership Seminar, Donald Weisstuch, 1999 September 29; cuid633; 11777 (Box 14, Folder 45)
    - Alumni Leadership Seminar, Tsuneo Nakahara, 1999 October 4; cuid634; 11753 (Box 14, Folder 46)
    - Alumni Leadership Seminar, John Wallace, 1999 October 27; cuid635; 11778 (Box 14, Folder 47)
    - Alumni Leadership Seminar, Dr. Peter Bingham, 2000 March 8; cuid636; 11759 (Box 14, Folder 48)
    - Alumni Leadership Seminar, Hazel O'Leary, 2000 October 18; cuid637; 11779 (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - Alumni Leadership Seminar, Barry Singer, 2001 February 28; cuid638; 11780 (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - Alumni Leadership Seminar, Daniel Robinson, 2001 April 4; cuid639; 11781 (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - Alumni Leadership Seminar, Michael Kappaz, 2001 April 16; cuid640; 11760 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Subseries E: Alumni Reunion, 13241
    - Annual Reunions, undated; cuid641; 11920 (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - Alumni Reunion 1986, cuid642; 13324 (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - Alumni Reunion 1993, cuid643; 11795 (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - Alumni Reunion 1996, 1996 June 8; cuid644; 11917 (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - Alumni Reunion 2002, 2002 June; cuid645; 11790 (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - Alumni Reunion of New York Society for Coatings Technology 1995, 1995 September 12; cuid646; 12809 (Box 15, Folder 10)
    - E.E. Reunion, 2000; cuid647; 13325 (Box 15, Folder 11)
    - Golden Jubilee 1966, 1966 June; cuid648; 11796 (Box 15, Folder 12)
    - Golden Jubilee 1967, 1967 June 15; cuid649; 11797 (Box 15, Folder 13)
    - Golden Jubilee 1984, 1984 July 26; cuid650; 13315 (Box 15, Folder 14)
    - Golden Jubilee 1993, 1993 June; cuid651; 11798 (Box 15, Folder 15)
    - Golden Jubilee 1998, 1998 June 7; cuid652; 11892 (Box 15, Folder 16)
    - Golden Jubilee 1999, 1999 June 5; cuid653; 11799 (Box 15, Folder 17)
    - Golden Jubilee 1999, 1999 June 5; cuid654; 11800 (Box 15, Folder 18)
    - Golden Jubilee 2000, 2000 June 5; cuid655; 11801 (Box 15, Folder 19)
    - Golden Jubilee 2001, 2001 June 2; cuid656; 11802 (Box 15, Folder 20)
    - Silver Jubilee 1999, 1999 June 8; cuid657; 12741 (Box 15, Folder 21)
    - Silver Jubilee 2001, 2001 June 11; cuid658; 12742 (Box 15, Folder 22)
    - Silver Jubilee Dinner 2001, 2001 June 5; cuid659; 12743 (Box 15, Folder 23)
- Series VII: Events, 9953
  - Subseries A: Freshman Week (Orientation), 9954
    - Freshman Week 1957, cuid660; 13113 (Box 15, Folder 24)
    - Freshman Week 1997, 1997 August 25; cuid661; 11812 (Box 15, Folder 25)
    - Freshman Week 1997, 1997 August 25; cuid662; 11813 (Box 15, Folder 26)
    - Freshman Week 1998, cuid663; 11814 (Box 15, Folder 27)
    - Freshman Week 1999, 1999 September 1; cuid664; 11815 (Box 15, Folder 28)
    - Freshman Week 2000, 2000 August; cuid665; 11816 (Box 15, Folder 29)
    - Freshman Week 2001, 2001 August 28; cuid666; 11817 (Box 15, Folder 30)
    - Freshman Week 2002, 2002 August 28; cuid667; 11818 (Box 15, Folder 31)
  - Subseries B: Commencement and Convocation, 11811
    - Commencement 1946, cuid668; 13327 (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Commencement 1952, cuid669; 11922 (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - Commencement 1956, cuid670; 11893 (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - Commencement 1958, cuid671; 11894 (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - Commencement 1959, cuid672; 13331 (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - Commencement 1960, cuid673; 11923 (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - Commencement 1961, cuid674; 13332 (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - Commencement 1962, cuid675; 13333 (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - Commencement 1963, cuid676; 11895 (Box 16, Folder 9)
    - Commencement 1964, cuid677; 13334 (Box 16, Folder 10)
    - Commencement 1965, cuid678; 13335 (Box 16, Folder 11)
    - Commencement 1966, cuid679; 11822 (Box 16, Folder 12)
    - Commencement 1967, cuid680; 11896 (Box 16, Folder 13)
    - Commencement 1967, cuid681; 13336 (Box 16, Folder 14)
    - Commencement 1968, cuid682; 11897 (Box 16, Folder 15)
    - Commencement 1969, cuid683; 11898 (Box 16, Folder 16)
    - Commencement 1971, cuid684; 11831 (Box 16, Folder 17)
    - Commencement 1972, cuid685; 11819 (Box 16, Folder 18)
    - Commencement 1973, cuid686; 11832 (Box 16, Folder 19)
    - Commencement 1974, cuid687; 11830 (Box 16, Folder 20)
    - Commencement 1975, 1975 May 30; cuid688; 11833 (Box 16, Folder 21)
    - Commencement 1976, cuid689; 11829 (Box 16, Folder 22)
    - Commencement 1980, cuid690; 11826 (Box 16, Folder 23)
    - Commencement 1981, cuid691; 11825 (Box 16, Folder 24)
    - Commencement 1982, cuid692; 11828 (Box 16, Folder 25)
    - Commencement 1983, cuid693; 11827 (Box 16, Folder 26)
    - Commencement 1985, cuid694; 11924 (Box 16, Folder 27)
    - Commencement 1986, cuid695; 11821 (Box 16, Folder 28)
    - Commencement 1987, 1987 June; cuid696; 11820 (Box 16, Folder 29)
    - Commencement 1988, cuid697; 11824 (Box 16, Folder 30)
    - Commencement 1989, cuid698; 11823 (Box 16, Folder 31)
    - Commencement 1993, cuid699; 11899 (Box 16, Folder 32)
    - Commencement 1994, cuid700; 11900 (Box 16, Folder 33)
    - Commencement 2010, cuid701; 11901 (Box 16, Folder 34)
    - Commencement undated, cuid702; 13326 (Box 16, Folder 35)
    - Convocation with Vance Packard, 1960s; cuid703; 13126 (Box 16, Folder 36)
    - Freshmen Parents at Convocation, 1960s; cuid704; 13128 (Box 16, Folder 37)
    - Convocation "Truth or Fiction" Lecture, 1960s; cuid705; 13129 (Box 16, Folder 38)
    - Convocation 1960s, cuid706; 13130 (Box 16, Folder 39)
    - Convocation 1966, 1966 December 14; cuid707; 13131 (Box 16, Folder 40)
    - Convocation 1968-1969, cuid708; 13127 (Box 16, Folder 41)
    - Convocation 1978, 1978 May 30; cuid709; 11925 (Box 16, Folder 42)
    - Convocation 1979, 1979 June 6; cuid710; 11926 (Box 16, Folder 43)
    - Convocation 2004, 2004 September 1; cuid711; 11927 (Box 16, Folder 44)
    - Westchester Convocation, 1985; cuid712; 13328 (Box 16, Folder 45)
    - Westchester Convocation Contact Sheets, 1986; cuid713; 13329 (Box 16, Folder 46)
    - Honorary Degree to Carey, 1975 March 13; cuid714; 13115 (Box 16, Folder 47)
    - Morris Chang Honorary Degree Ceremony, 1999; cuid715; 13330 (Box 16, Folder 48)
  - Subseries C: Groundbreakings and Dedications, 10862
    - Abacus Sculpture Dedication, 1993; cuid716; 13117 (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - Abacus, 1999 October; cuid717; 13023 (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - Center for Finance & Technology, 1996; cuid718; 12844 (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - Center for Fire Safety Engineering, 2002 April 9; cuid719; 12845 (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - David Conklin Lab Dedication, 1998 May 18; cuid720; 13256 (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - Dibner Library/CATT Building Groundbreaking, 1990; cuid721; 13251 (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - Dibner Building Dedication, 1990; cuid722; 13046 (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - Dibner/CATT Dedication, 1992; cuid723; 13050 (Box 17, Folder 8)
    - Dibner/CATT Dedication- Building and MetroTech Views, 1992; cuid724; 13051 (Box 17, Folder 9)
    - Dibner/CATT Building, 1990s; cuid725; 12841 (Box 17, Folder 10)
    - Dibner Media Lab Dedication, 2000 April 26; cuid726; 13047 (Box 17, Folder 11)
    - Jacobs Building and Jacobs Way Dedication, 1998 June; cuid727; 13049 (Box 17, Folder 12)
    - Jacobs Building Groundbreaking, 2000 May 18; cuid728; 13252 (Box 17, Folder 13)
    - Jacobs Building Groundbreaking, 2000 May 18; cuid729; 13253 (Box 17, Folder 14)
    - Jacobs Building Groundbreaking, 2000 May 18; cuid730; 13254 (Box 17, Folder 15)
    - Jacobs Building Groundbreaking, 2000 May 18; cuid731; 13027 (Box 17, Folder 16)
    - Jacobs Building Groundbreaking, 2000 May 18; cuid732; 13030 (Box 17, Folder 17)
    - Jacobs Building Construction- Soil Boring Test, 1998 November 9; cuid733; 13255 (Box 17, Folder 18)
    - Jacobs Construction, 2001 October 5; cuid734; 12854 (Box 17, Folder 19)
    - Jacobs Dedication Ceremony, 2002 June 13; cuid735; 13048 (Box 17, Folder 20)
    - Jacobs Dedication Ceremony, 2002 June 13; cuid736; 13257 (Box 17, Folder 21)
    - Jacobs Building and Othmer Residence Hall Dedication, 2002 June 13; cuid737; 13045 (Box 17, Folder 22)
    - Jacobs Building Dedication Awards, 2002 October 23; cuid738; 12910 (Box 17, Folder 23)
    - Topping Off Ceremony- Jacobs Building, 2001 May 18; cuid739; 13002 (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - Topping Off Ceremony- Othmer Dorms, 2001 July 26; cuid740; 13040 (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - Regna Lounge Dedication, 2003 October 7; cuid741; 12978 (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - Rogers Hall Dedication, circa 1957; cuid742; 13044 (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - Sculpture Dedication and Lynford Lecture with Robert Mundell, 2002 October 8; cuid743; 12987 (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - Sperry Dedication, undated; cuid744; 13043 (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - Tour of Media Lab, 1999 October 15; cuid745; 13003 (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - Wunsch Lab Dedication, 1965 May 14; cuid746; 13184 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Subseries D: Banquets and Celebrations, 12052
    - 21 Club Dinner, 1994; cuid747; 13337 (Box 18, Folder 9)
    - Awards Ceremony, 1995; cuid748; 13338 (Box 18, Folder 10)
    - Buecke Dinner, undated; cuid749; 13341 (Box 18, Folder 11)
    - Corporation Dinner 1976, cuid750; 13346 (Box 18, Folder 12)
    - Corporation Dinner 1979, cuid751; 13347 (Box 18, Folder 13)
    - Corporation Dinner 1981, cuid752; 13348 (Box 18, Folder 14)
    - Corporation Dinner 1982, cuid753; 13349 (Box 18, Folder 15)
    - Corporation Dinner 1984, cuid754; 13350 (Box 18, Folder 16)
    - Corporation Dinner 1985, cuid755; 13351 (Box 18, Folder 17)
    - Corporation Dinner 1986, cuid756; 13159 (Box 18, Folder 18)
    - Cuomo Dinner, undated; cuid757; 13345 (Box 18, Folder 19)
    - Dinner with Ernst Weber, undated; cuid758; 13116 (Box 18, Folder 20)
    - Dinners, 1967-1968, cuid759; 13118 (Box 18, Folder 21)
    - Dinners, Undated, cuid760; 13352 (Box 18, Folder 22)
    - Dinners and Dances, 1954-1987; cuid761; 13132 (Box 18, Folder 23)
    - Executive Breakfast, 2000 March; cuid762; 13391 (Box 18, Folder 24)
    - Executive Breakfast, 2003 February; cuid763; 13343 (Box 18, Folder 25)
    - George Bugliarello Tribute, 1994; cuid764; 13339 (Box 18, Folder 26)
    - Goldsmith's Birthday Party, 1999 October 18; cuid765; 13344 (Box 18, Folder 27)
    - Hallingby Dinner, 1987 June; cuid766; 13353 (Box 18, Folder 28)
    - Holiday Party 1994, 1994 December 19; cuid767; 12785 (Box 18, Folder 29)
    - Holiday Party 1995, 1995 December; cuid768; 12763 (Box 18, Folder 30)
    - Holiday Party 1997, 1997 December; cuid769; 12764 (Box 18, Folder 31)
    - Holiday Party 1999, 1999 December; cuid770; 12762 (Box 18, Folder 32)
    - Holiday Party 2000, 2000 December 11; cuid771; 12758 (Box 18, Folder 33)
    - Holiday Party 2001, 2001 December 13; cuid772; 12761 (Box 18, Folder 34)
    - Jack Kueler Dinner, 1991; cuid773; 13368 (Box 18, Folder 35)
    - Kwanzaa Celebration, 2000 December 8; cuid774; 13354 (Box 18, Folder 36)
    - Long Island Leadership Dinner, 1989 November 1; cuid775; 13356 (Box 18, Folder 37)
    - Long Island Dinner 1983, cuid776; 13355 (Box 18, Folder 38)
    - Long Island Dinner 1985, cuid777; 13340 (Box 18, Folder 39)
    - Luncheons, 1953-1954; cuid778; 13357 (Box 18, Folder 40)
    - PA Dinner, 1992; cuid779; 13358 (Box 18, Folder 41)
    - Poly Ventures Dinner, 1987; cuid780; 13359 (Box 18, Folder 42)
    - President Associate's Dinner 1987-1988, cuid781; 13360 (Box 18, Folder 43)
    - President Associate's Dinner 1992, cuid782; 12011 (Box 18, Folder 44)
    - President Associate's Dinner 1993, cuid783; 12012 (Box 18, Folder 45)
    - President Associate's Dinner 1994, cuid784; 12013 (Box 18, Folder 46)
    - President Associate's Dinner 1995, 1995 September 28; cuid785; 12009 (Box 18, Folder 47)
    - President Associate's Dinner 1996, 1996 October 25; cuid786; 12010 (Box 18, Folder 48)
    - President Associate's Dinner 1998, 1998 October 13; cuid787; 12708 (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - President Associate's Dinner 1999, 1999 October 5; cuid788; 12008 (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - President Associate's Dinner 2000, 2000 October 12; cuid789; 12709 (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - President's Reception, 1983; cuid790; 13361 (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - Sunil's Farewell Party, undated; cuid791; 13363 (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - Tech Leadership Award Dinner, 1990; cuid792; 13364 (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - Various Dinners and Celebrations, undated; cuid793; 13147 (Box 19, Folder 7)
    - Westchester Dinner 1987, cuid794; 13365 (Box 19, Folder 8)
    - Westchester Dinner negatives 1990, cuid795; 13366 (Box 19, Folder 9)
    - West Coast Tech Awards Dinner, undated; cuid796; 13367 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Subseries E: Visiting Individuals and Groups, 12765
    - Alumni Astronauts Visit, 2015; cuid797; 14462 (Box 19, Folder 10.1)
    - Betty Wu Visit, 2002 May; cuid798; 12808 (Box 19, Folder 11)
    - Bjarne Stroustrup Visit, 2002 April 9; cuid799; 12772 (Box 19, Folder 12)
    - Brooklyn Institutional Council, undated; cuid800; 13370 (Box 19, Folder 13)
    - Brooklyn Union Gas, 1927 October 25; cuid801; 13369 (Box 19, Folder 14)
    - Charles DeBenedittis Visit, 2002 October 28; cuid802; 12784 (Box 19, Folder 15)
    - Chinese Delegation Visit, undated; cuid803; 13158 (Box 19, Folder 16)
    - Con Edison Visit, 1993 May 11; cuid804; 12786 (Box 19, Folder 17)
    - Congelese Student Visit, 1961 November; cuid805; 13119 (Box 19, Folder 18)
    - David Dibner Visit, 1998 May; cuid806; 12775 (Box 19, Folder 19)
    - Desiree Ruhstrat Visit, 1998 June 9; cuid807; 12778 (Box 19, Folder 20)
    - Eugene Kleiner Visit, 1996 September 20; cuid808; 12777 (Box 19, Folder 21)
    - Eugene Kleiner Visit, 1998 April 2; cuid809; 12776 (Box 19, Folder 22)
    - General Council of China Visit, 1997 February 26; cuid810; 12779 (Box 19, Folder 23)
    - Groups- Miscellaneous, 1938-1963; cuid811; 13371 (Box 19, Folder 24)
    - Martin Perl Visit, 1996 May 29; cuid812; 12783 (Box 19, Folder 25)
    - Martin Perl Visit, 1998 May; cuid813; 12782 (Box 19, Folder 26)
    - Marty Markowitz Visit, 2002 February 4; cuid814; 12781 (Box 19, Folder 27)
    - Mayor's Cabinet Meeting, 1968; cuid815; 13138 (Box 19, Folder 28)
    - Michael Bloomberg Visit, 2003 August 6; cuid816; 12780 (Box 19, Folder 29)
    - Paul Soros Visit, 1997 April 24; cuid817; 12767 (Box 19, Folder 30)
    - Robert Tsao Visit, undated; cuid818; 12771 (Box 19, Folder 31)
    - Saul Harari Visit, 2003 November; cuid819; 12774 (Box 19, Folder 32)
    - Stephen Wolfram Visit, 2003 March 5; cuid820; 12773 (Box 19, Folder 33)
    - Sumitomo Electric Inc. USA Visit, 1997 November 7; cuid821; 12770 (Box 19, Folder 34)
    - Taiwan University Dignitaries Visit, 1998 August; cuid822; 12769 (Box 19, Folder 35)
    - Walter Rosenberry, 1998 September 25; cuid823; 12768 (Box 19, Folder 36)
  - Subseries F: Symposia and Presentations, 12766
    - ACS Symposium, 1999 April 29; cuid824; 13021 (Box 19, Folder 37)
    - Centennial Exhibit at Brooklyn Public Library, 1954; cuid825; 13122 (Box 19, Folder 38)
    - College Partnership Symposium, 1998; cuid826; 13372 (Box 19, Folder 39)
    - Conference on High Speed Aeronautics, circa 1960; cuid827; 13133 (Box 19, Folder 40)
    - Future of Telecommunications Symposium, 2005 February 11; cuid828; 12725 (Box 19, Folder 41)
    - Gene Delivery Symposium, 2000 June 19; cuid829; 12810 (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - Herman Mark Symposium, 1975 May 2-3; cuid830; 12801 (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - Herman Mark Memorial Symposium, 1992; cuid831; 12800 (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - Hoerscht Celanese Yearly Presentation, 1997; cuid832; 13373 (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - International Conference on Business Incubation and Technology Innovation, 2000; cuid833; 13374 (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - Leadership Seminar 1994, cuid834; 13375 (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - Leadership Seminar 1995, cuid835; 13376 (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - Lectures/Symposia- various, 1920s - 1950s; cuid836; 13377 (Box 20, Folder 8)
    - Leibniz Symposium, 1960s; cuid837; 13137 (Box 20, Folder 9)
    - Lucent Technologies Check Presentation 1996, 1996 December 19; cuid838; 12805 (Box 20, Folder 10)
    - Lucent Technologies Check Presentation 1999, 1999 December; cuid839; 12806 (Box 20, Folder 11)
    - ME100: 100 Years of Mechanical Engineering at Poly 1899-1999, 1999 November 4-5; cuid840; 12796 (Box 20, Folder 12)
    - ME100: 100 Years of Mechanical Engineering at Poly 1899-1999, 1999 November 4-5; cuid841; 12797 (Box 20, Folder 13)
    - ME100: 100 Years of Mechanical Engineering at Poly 1899-1999, 1999 November 4-5; cuid842; 12798 (Box 20, Folder 14)
    - MMC-9 Conference, 2001 August 19-23; cuid843; 12799 (Box 20, Folder 15)
    - Othmer Symposium, 2002 October 8; cuid844; 13378 (Box 20, Folder 16)
    - Polymer Symposium, 1985; cuid845; 13380 (Box 20, Folder 17)
    - Polytechnic Centennial 1954-1955, 1954 December - 1955 July; cuid846; 12802 (Box 20, Folder 18)
    - Polytechnic Centennial 1954-1955, cuid847; 12803 (Box 20, Folder 19)
    - Polytechnic Centennial 1954-1955, cuid848; 12804 (Box 20, Folder 20)
    - Principal's Symposium, 1998 March-May; cuid849; 13379 (Box 20, Folder 21)
    - Saline Water Meeting, 1965; cuid850; 13134 (Box 20, Folder 22)
    - Symposium on Advances in Chelate Chemistry, 1955; cuid851; 13381 (Box 20, Folder 23)
    - Tic Tac Tones, 1960s; cuid852; 13135 (Box 20, Folder 24)
    - Urban Transportation Seminar, 1960s; cuid853; 13136 (Box 20, Folder 25)
  - Subseries G: Lynford Lecture Series, 12787
    - Lynford Dinner, 1997 September 24; cuid854; 12792 (Box 20, Folder 26)
    - Lynford Lecture Series- Ed Witten 1998, 1998 September 15; cuid855; 12793 (Box 20, Folder 27)
    - Lynford Lecture Series- John Craig Venter 1999, 1999 October 13; cuid856; 12788 (Box 20, Folder 28)
    - Lynford Lecture Series- Bill Joy 2000, 2000 October 12; cuid857; 12789 (Box 20, Folder 29)
    - Lynford Lecture Series- Dr. Alan Kay 2001, 2001 October 9; cuid858; 12790 (Box 20, Folder 30)